auroin.com 2009-11-30

# Search Engine Optimization Services in India | Read Privacy Policy for Services

Auroinfotech Solutions, the best search engine optimization services provider of India, has its own privacy policy and always follows it strictly. This privacy Policy is exclusively meant for the use of information and other resources of Auroinfotech Solutions’s official web site [(](http://www.auroin.com/)[http://www.auroin.com](http://www.auroin.com/ "http://www.auroin.com")). The privacy policy acquaints you with the following points:

  * Privacy to collected information.
  * How you are facilitated to use Auroinfotech Solutions’s information and other resources.
  * The security methods in order to guard the abuse of the information provided by you.
  * How you are facilitated to modify any factual errors in your given information.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  
Auroinfotech Solutions is the sole owners of all the given information on this site. Only the officials and executive body members have access to, collect and use the information that you have willingly given us via email or other medium of contact. We respect your intention, thus your given information is hereby ensured not to be used for any other purpose which may hamper your personal benefit.  
Your given information will be used for your purpose and while contacting you in response to the reason of your contact. Without your consent, your given information won’t be shared with any third party outside our company. If the urgency is there, then you will be immediately contacted.  
As our company strategy, we may contact you via email in the future to convey you regarding specials, launching of new products or services, or any other modifications to this privacy policy, unless you ask us not to do so.  
Your Access to and Control Over Information  
You are allowed to contact us at any time from anywhere only for beneficiary purpose. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email given on our Contact Us page.

Security  
Auroinfotech Solutions has taken all precautions in order to protect all information. Here “information” can be realized as the information given by you and its own information. Auroinfotech Solutions has three level accesses to all the information. The Management body has complete access to all kinds of information without any body’s consent; the officials have access to the information, for which they are allowed to; and the associates for whom Auroinfotech Solutions is working can access to the information for which they will be allowed to. Your information (as we consider it the most sensitive and strategic one) is protected under any Internet Information Violation Act, India and immediate legal action can be taken against the violated person strictly after Management Board’s decision. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.  
Contact Form  
In order to contact us for any purpose you, a user must fulfill all the mandatory fields so that we can get sufficient information about the user. These mandatory information are Name, Authentic Email ID at least. This information will be used to contact you for other promotional purpose only.  
Links  
Auroinfotech Solutions’s official web site contains links to other sites. But, we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those websites. 

We encourage our users to be aware of the above privacy points, when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Our users are always welcome to suggest anything which can strengthen our security and privacy level. Thank you for visiting this page.
